these
love the path to happiness
so
just nature and nature of love in
general well
the short answer is absolutely not
because the common phenomenon of love is
the common phenomenon of love is
inseparable from attachment and
but if you're not attached to something
you're not loving it so the whole notion
of you know the unconditional love well
it's a contradiction in terms
you're either unconditionally
bound with it or you you're emotionally
divorced from it which means you don't
love it which means you're not attached
to it so is
in itself love is is a bond even you can
make it as abstract and divine as you
want it's still a bond because it still
has its object which means there is
still some sort of attachment just to
the two-degree but
actually like that's just people's
fantasy very often when we talk about
the unconditional love and like an idea
of an abstract ideal that in practice
love this it's it even worse it's it's
always in fact it's always mixed with
infatuation with lust with the light
with conceit with pride with everything
else that basically will love it passion
of course inseparable from passion
well I'm sure the people who try to
justify the log they would think that
yeah
that is just an idea basically that you
can't that it's a contradiction in terms
because if you're well
if you're well
loved be even unconditional is a
relationship means
you are you are relating yourself to
these things which means to that extent
you're bound by them so
it's impossible to have unconditional
love if it's unconditioned means there
is no condition there is no relationship
but love is a relationship so it's
basically saying like oh the
unconditional condition the
unconditionally conditioned that's what
unconditional love would be or
have a relationship with no relationship
that just that's a contradiction in
terms so you can find that poetic value
in insane contradictory terms but in
itself in the practice and finally
logically speaking makes absolutely no
sense so
you're either bound or you're free from
the bound from there from the bond well
it depends but no no I mean love can be
wholesome that's
one sort of slow in answering love can
be wholesome in a sense of it's not
necessarily you know infatuated
passion and lust and greed involved with
it but as a bond as something that is
fundamentally still rooted in in a
degree of passion and and emotion
it is unwholesome from the point of view
of enlightenment it is it is unwholesome
it's an obstacle base it's a it's a it's
a bond that you need to break yeah
love or hate basically if you want to be free
or hate basically if you want to be free
from suffering or if you want to develop
your mind to the well its full potential
so to speak potential freedom both
must be abandoned equally both
love and hate it
can bring world happiness which from the
other point of view it's not happiness
obviously